- Please, I'm begging you, go to sleep.
- I'm trying. I'm counting Catwomen.
(Sheldon:)She did make a fine mutant
in the X-Men movies, though.
(Howard:)Oh, for God's sake.
She's not my favorite of the X-Men.
In order, that'd be Wolverine, Cyclops...
(Sheldon:)I forgot Professor X.
Professor X, Wolverine, Cyclops, Iceman...
(Sheldon:)...then Storm, Angel, the Bea...
No, wait, Nightcrawler.
(Sheldon:)Professor X, Nightcrawler, Wolverine,
Cyclops, Iceman, then Storm, Angel...
[DOOR KNOCKS]
LEONARD:
I'm coming.
(Leonard:)Hey.
(Sheldon:)There he is.
There's my old buddy-bud-bud.
- What's with him?
- Koothrappali dumped him on me.
(Howard:)He couldn't get to sleep,
so I gave him a glass of milk...
(Howard:)...with a handful
of my mom's Valium in it.
(Howard:)But he still wouldn't shut up,
so tag, you're it.